Azizul Hakim

Computer Science Student



CAREER OBJECTIVE

Second year Computer Science student seeking to use my academic knowledge in a co-op position. Possess more than 1 year of hands-on experience building and testing programs in different languages like Java, C++, C and JavaScript. A motivated individual with strong communication skills and problem-solving skills.



EXPERIENCE

Banquet Server

Era Bistro and Catering, Winnipeg, MB / Jan 2018-Present

- Assisting guests with making menu choices in an informative and helpful way.
- Delivering exceptional, fast and friendly service.
- maintaining a congenial relationship with the Co-workers and the quests.

Server and Bartender

University of Manitoba Catering Services, Winnipeg, MB / Mar 2019–Present

- Preparing alcoholic or non-alcoholic beverages for bar and patrons.
- Interacting with customers, taking orders and serving snacks and drinks.

Voluntary Math Tutor

Frontier College, Winnipeg, MB / Sep 2017-Apr 2018

- Assisting kids from grades (1-8) with their homework.
- Improving their ideas on Math and maintaining a friendly relationship with the students.

Sustainability Ambassador

University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, MB / Sep 2019-present

- Provide guidance to students who want to plan sustainable events.
- Volunteer in many different sustainable events.
- Provide information to everyone on campus about sustainability and Sustainable resources.



CONTACT

Email:

hakima@myumanitoba.ca

Phone:

2048991451

Address:

134-150 Baylor Avenue, Winnipeg, MB

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/azizul-hakim-41862b1a2/

Github:

github.com/AzizulHakim96



PROJECTS

Connect4 game in Java

Online ordering System

Student Help Portal

Personal Website



HARD SKILLS

Java, C, C++, SQL,

JavaScript, Python, HTML,

CSS, Linux, Lc-3 Assembly,

Microsoft Office, Aws, Data

Entry



EDUCATION

B.S. / COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, Manitoba 2017-2022